https://afsinsurance.com/privacy/

PRIVACY POLICY
We would like to take this opportunity to both thank you for visiting our website and to share with you the importance  Ahart, Frinzi & Smith places upon protecting your private information.
Collection of Information
While you are visiting our website, we may or may not collect personal/confidential information-written, in person, telephone, facsimile, electronically and online-that may assist us in preparing a quotation for you and in helping us to negotiate with our carriers on your behalf. The personal information we collect may include your name, address, policy or claim information, financial or other information as may be required by our underwriters.
We also collect personal information about you from the following sources: (1) Applications or other forms such as claims forms or underwriting questionnaires that you submit to us and others; (2) Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others; and (3) Third party information from public sources such as the internet or governmental agencies.
Disclosure of Information:
We assure you that is not our policy to share your private information with non-affiliated third parties other than as permitted or required by law. For example, we may share all of the information listed above with non-affiliated third parties for, including but not limited to, the following reasons:
The information is essential in servicing or processing the insurance needs of our clients in a way that is customary and necessary among Independent Insurance agents in our industry. Our services and processes might include, for example, but are not limited to, underwriting, obtaining renewal terms, rating, placement and providing quotes for insurance that is germane to the coverage the customer places with our agency.
Information necessary to protect the confidentiality or security of our client’s records.
Information necessary to resolve client disputes or inquires.
Information required by individuals or entities who are assessing our legal compliance.
Information required for us to comply with the law.
Information necessary to protect against or prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims or other liability.
Protection of Information:
Our Agency maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with state and federal regulations to protect the confidentiality of your personal information.
We appreciate your business and in order to continue building upon that relationship, believe it is necessary not only from a legal standpoint but also as a sound business practice that you, our customer, understand the care our agency uses in handling your information. Our Agency will continue to monitor the effectiveness of this privacy policy.
Ahart, Frinzi, & Smith
2250 Belvidere Rd
Phillipsburg, NJ 08865
Get directions
(703) 299-4207
(908) 454 - 4170
quote@afsinsurance.com
Alexandria,VA Location
127 S Peyton St.
#201
Alexandria, VA 22314
Get directions
(703) 299-4207
(703) 299-4207
quote@afsinsurance.com
Ready to save time, aggravation, and money?
Start Your Quotes Here
New Jersey Location
Ahart, Frinzi, & Smith
2250 Belvidere Rd
Phillipsburg, NJ 08865
Get directions
(703) 299-4207
(908) 454 - 4170
quote@afsinsurance.com
Helpful Links
Privacy Policy
Virginia Location
Alexandria,VA Location
127 S Peyton St.
#201
Alexandria, VA 22314
Get directions
(703) 299-4207
(703) 299-4207
quote@afsinsurance.com
Connect With Us on Facebook
Ahart, Frinzi & Smith
Contact Us
Ask us anything!
×
Send Message In App
Client Update
We are taking the necessary precautions to keep our staff and community safe. Many of us are working from home but continue to serve our clients by calling in for messages and checking emails frequently. Please know we are here for you in every capacity we can be. Stay safe-we can get through this together.
CLOSE
Skip to content
Open toolbar
Accessibility Tools
Increase Text
Decrease Text
Grayscale
High Contrast
